=Seal of Love= (Season 1)
= ختم الحب = (الموسم الأول)
=Episode 2=
= الحلقة 2 =
(With my spirit,)
(بروحي)
(your soul will be cleaned.)
(سيتم تنظيف روحك).
(When the Fire burned the Three Realms, all devils died.)
(عندما أحرقت النار العوالم الثلاثة ، مات كل الشياطين).
Why did she save no one but me?
لماذا لم تنقذ أحدا سواي؟
(It's been a thousand years.)
(لقد مرت ألف عام).
(My Lord, don't bother about it anymore.)
(ربي ، لا تهتم بهذا الأمر بعد الآن.)
(Your top priority is to breach the seal.)
(أولويتك القصوى هي خرق الختم.)
Keep quiet and go.
حافظ على الهدوء وانطلق.
Go.
يذهب.
Look what we've got, immortal disciples.
انظروا إلى ما لدينا ، أيها التلاميذ الخالدون.
Her Grace is brilliant.
لها نعمة رائعة.
- Yeah. We count on Her Grace. - I heard Her Grace only used one stroke
- نعم.  نحن نعتمد على نعمتها.  - سمعت أن جريس لها استخدمت فقط ضربة واحدة
and defeated so many of them.
وهزمت الكثير منهم.
Amazing.
مدهش.
Go.
يذهب.
Kneel.
اركع.
Disciples of the Immortal Spirit Sect
تلاميذ طائفة الروح الخالدة
are said to be very powerful.
يُقال إنها قوية جدًا.
Well, I don't think so.
حسنًا ، لا أعتقد ذلك.
When Lord Qing Chen comes out, you'll be in trouble.
عندما يخرج اللورد تشينغ تشين ، ستكون في مأزق.
Lord Qing Chen?
اللورد تشينغ تشن؟
I've heard about him.
سمعت عنه.
He's said to be clever
يقال إنه ذكي
and gentle.
ولطيف.
But I've never met him before.
لكني لم أقابله من قبل.
How dare you say such stuff about Lord Qing Chen!
كيف تجرؤ على قول مثل هذه الأشياء عن اللورد تشينغ تشن!
(Hongshao, a demon disciple)
(Hongshao ، تلميذ شيطاني)
What do you think of this indirect attack?
ما رأيك في هذا الهجوم غير المباشر؟
I used only a little bit of power.
لقد استخدمت القليل من القوة فقط.
Or your face would have been disfigured.
أو قد تشوه وجهك.
Could you please let them go?
هل يمكنك السماح لهم بالذهاب من فضلك؟
You have a nice voice.
لديك صوت جميل.
You're in good shape, too.
أنت في حالة جيدة أيضًا.
You're as gentle as you're said to be.
أنت لطيف كما يقال.
I just wonder
انى اتسائل فقط
if you're really sweet, too.
إذا كنت حقا لطيفا أيضا.
What a demon! You're a woman,
يا له من شيطان!  انت امراة
but look how shameless you are!
لكن انظر كم أنت وقح!
What on earth do you want?
ماذا تريد بحق الارض؟
I think
أظن
you look like an old friend of mine.
تبدو كصديق قديم لي.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Qing Chen.
تشينغ تشن.
I'll call you Qing.
سأتصل بك تشينغ.
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
If your face is handsome enough, I'll let them go.
إذا كان وجهك وسيمًا بدرجة كافية ، فسأطلق سراحهم.
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
I don't want to fight a lady.
لا أريد أن أقاتل سيدة.
But I request you
لكني أطلب منك
to let go of my disciples.
لأترك تلاميذي.
Oh, boring.
أوه ، ممل.
But you know what?
ولكن هل تعلم؟
I really want to see your face.
انا حقا اريد ان ارى وجهك
Aah!
آآآه!
You...
أنت...
A lord like you used a dirty trick?
رب مثلك استخدم خدعة قذرة؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
(I got you, huh?)
(لقد حصلت عليك ، أليس كذلك؟)
(He's indeed the Most Handsome Immortal.)
(إنه حقًا أكثر الخالد وسامة).
(Her face...)
(وجهها...)
(Xiyun?)
(شييون؟)
(Qing Chen,)
(تشينغ تشن)
(when flowers bloom next year,)
(عندما تتفتح الأزهار العام المقبل)
(defend the Three Realms for me.)
(دافع عن العوالم الثلاثة من أجلي.)
♪Away you sail in a white robe♪
تبحر في رداء أبيض
(He's staring at me.)
(إنه يحدق بي).
(It... It can't be.)
(إنه ... لا يمكن أن يكون.)
♪When snow is boiled and spring comes♪
عندما يغلي الثلج ويأتي الربيع ♪
♪You and I shall get hammered♪
أنت وأنا سوف نُطرَق ♪
♪Stars are around the moon and it's too late at night♪
♪ النجوم حول القمر وقد فات الأوان في الليل
I'm done looking at your face.
لقد انتهيت من النظر إلى وجهك.
♪When sobering up don't lean on the rails♪
عند الاستيقاظ ، لا تتكئ على القضبان ♪
What about you, Lord Qing Chen?
ماذا عنك يا لورد تشينغ تشن؟
♪Old clothes are nowhere to be seen♪
الملابس القديمة لا يمكن رؤيتها في أي مكان
What's this about?
ما هذا؟
What happened just now?
ماذا حدث للتو؟
What magic is that?
ما هذا السحر؟
♪I travel all over the world singing and drinking♪
♪ أسافر حول العالم أغني وأشرب
♪I ride around from north to south♪
أتجول من الشمال إلى الجنوب
Your Grace, where are they?
نعمتك أين هم؟
They escaped.
لقد هربوا.
Escaped? How come?
هرب؟  كيف ذلك؟
♪Who loves power and fight♪
♪ من يحب القوة والقتال ♪
♪Locking himself away with nature♪
حبس نفسه بعيدًا عن الطبيعة
♪With too much to worry about You stay all alone♪
مع الكثير مما يدعو للقلق بشأن بقائك وحدك
♪Back there snow billows through the air♪
مرة أخرى هناك يتدفق الثلج في الهواء ♪
Yeah.
نعم.
They escaped like cowards.
هربوا مثل الجبناء.
♪In the next life May everything be in peace♪
في الحياة الآخرة ، عسى أن يكون كل شيء في سلام
♪Back in the hometown Obsessions linger♪
♪ العودة في مسقط رأس الهواجس باقية ♪
♪Pursuing the skinny love I just can't get over it♪
♪ أسعى وراء الحب النحيف الذي لا يمكنني تجاوزه
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪